YOU ARE HERE
CONVENIENCE STORE OWSON
KISARA DRUGSTORE
SOBA SHOP ARISUGAWA
TAILOR TANAKA
EPISODE 17
ROHAN KISHIBE'S ADVENTURE
YONEMORI
HONMA
ONODERA
NUMAKURA
ROCKY
BOOM
SNAP
DRIP
REVERB
CRASH
BOOM
FAMILY MASSACRE CASE
REMAINS MYSTERY
SUGIMOTO FAMILY GRAVE
SUGIMOTO
REIMI
SUGIMOTO FAMILY GRAVE
MORIOH LANDMARK 6
"GHOST ALLEY"
HOW TO GET THERE: TAKE #11 BUS
FROM MORIOH STATION
TO KOTODAI SHOPPING DISTRICT.
THE ALLEY LIES BETWEEN
THE OWSON CONVENIENCE STORE
AND KISARA DRUGSTORE AT 2-CHOME.
BEWARE: IF YOU ARE ONE OF THE FEW
WHO CAN SEE THE ALLEY AND
HAPPEN TO WANDER INTO ITS DEPTHS,
DO NOT LOOK BACK, NO MATTER WHAT.
KIRA
EPISODE 18
SHIGECHI'S HARVEST, PART 1